https://www.wbdoors.com/terms-conditions-williams-brothers

Menu
HOMECOMPANY PROFILEAbout UsThe Williams Brothers DifferenceACCESS DOORS & PANELSGeneral Purpose Access DoorsFire-Rated Access DoorsDrywall Access DoorsGFRG Hidden Access PanelsExterior Access Doors for Outside UseAluminum Access DoorsSecurity Access DoorsPlaster Bead Access DoorsAcoustical Tile Access DoorsAirtight / Watertight Access DoorsPlastic Access DoorsDuct Access Doors for HVACAccess Door Accessories (PDF)Specialty Access Doors & PanelsAccess Doors for Air & Dust ControlAccess Doors for TileAccess Doors with WindowFlorida Approved Exterior DoorsRain Guard Access Door with Insect NetRecessed Access DoorsSound Rated Access DoorsSuspended Ceiling Access DoorsTouch Latch Access Doors with No CamsVented/Louvered Access DoorsView AllROOF HATCHES & FLOOR DOORSWB Roof HatchesWB Fire & Smoke VentsWB Roof Hatch Railing SystemsWB Floor Hatches & DoorsBilco Floor Doors & HatchesLadders & Safety PostsRESOURCESArchitectural Specification Form (Word)Submittal SheetsCross Reference GuidesCertifications & Approvals (PDF)Current Catalog (PDF)VideosWarrantyReturnsTerms & ConditionsREQUEST QUOTE
Access Doors & PanelsGeneral Purpose Access DoorsFire-Rated Access DoorsDrywall Access DoorsPlaster Bead Access DoorsGFRG Hidden Access PanelsAcoustical Tile Access DoorsSecurity Access DoorsExterior Access DoorsAluminum Access DoorsAirtight / Watertight Access DoorsPlastic Access DoorsDuct Access DoorsAccess Door Accessories (PDF)View AllSpecialty Access Doors & PanelsAccess Doors for Air & Dust ControlAccess Doors for TileAccess Doors with WindowFlorida Approved Exterior DoorsRain Guard Door with Insect NetRecessed Access DoorsRound Metal Access DoorsSound Rated Access DoorsSuspended Ceiling Access DoorsTouch Latch Doors with No CamsVented/Louvered Access DoorsRoof Hatches & Floor DoorsWB Roof HatchesWB Fire & Smoke VentsWB Roof Hatch Railing SystemsWB Floor Hatches & DoorsBilco Floor Doors & HatchesLadders & Safety Posts
Terms and Conditions | Williams Brothers
In using this website you are deemed to have read and agreed to the following terms and conditions:
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all Agreements: "Client", “You”
and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the Company’s terms and conditions. "The Company", “Ourselves”, “We”
and "Us", refers to our Company. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves. All
terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the
most appropriate manner, whether by formal meetings of a fixed duration, or any other means, for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s
needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services/products, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing English Law. Any use
of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore
as referring to same.
Privacy Statement:
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized employees within the company on a need to know basis only use any information collected
from individual customers. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our customers. Parliament has created
specific offences for unauthorised actions against computer systems and data. We will investigate any such actions with a view to prosecuting
and/or taking civil proceedings to recover damages against those responsible
Confidentiality:
We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent
by this Company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.
Disclaimer:
Exclusions and Limitations The information on this web site is provided on an "as is" basis. To the fullest extent permitted by law, this Company:
excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any
other third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the Company’s literature; and excludes all
liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of
business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things or you have advised this
Company of the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your computer, computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon
or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages. This Company does not however exclude liability for death or personal
injury caused by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights
as a consumer are affected.
Payment:
Cash or Personal Cheque with Bankers Card, all major Credit/Debit Cards, Bankers Draft or BACS Transfer are all acceptable
methods of payment. Our Terms are payment in full on order. All goods remain the property of the Company until paid for in full. Monies that
remains outstanding by the due date will incur late payment interest at the rate of 2% above the prevailing Bank of America's base rate on
the outstanding balance until such time as the balance is paid in full and final settlement. We reserve the right to seek recovery of any monies
remaining unpaid sixty days from the date of invoice via collection Agencies and/or through the Small Claims Court in the event that the outstanding
balance does not exceed $5000. In such circumstances, you shall be liable for any and all additional administrative and/or court costs. Returned
cheques will incur a $45 charge to cover banking fees and administrative costs. In an instance of a second Returned cheque, we reserve the
right to terminate the arrangement and, if agreed to, we shall insist on future cash transactions only. Consequently, all bookings and/or transactions
and agreements entered into will cease with immediate effect until such time as any and all outstanding monies are recovered in full. Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and
troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL
requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within this Company on a need-to-know basis.
Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit
permission. Links to this website You may not create a link to any page of this website without our prior written consent. If you do create
a link to a page of this website you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this
website by linking to it.
Links From This Website:
We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed
or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions
or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be
aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of
any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company
will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties
of personal information. Communication We have several different e-mail addresses for different queries. These, & other contact information,
can be found on our Contact Us link on our website or via Company literature or via the Company’s stated telephone, facsimile or mobile telephone
numbers.
Force Majeure
Neither party shall be liable to the other for any failure to perform any obligation under any Agreement which is due to an event beyond the control
of such party including but not limited to any Act of God, terrorism, war, Political insurgence, insurrection, riot, civil unrest, act of civil
or military authority, uprising, earthquake, flood or any other natural or man made eventuality outside of our control, which causes the termination
of an agreement or contract entered into, nor which could have been reasonably foreseen. Any Party affected by such event shall forthwith inform
the other Party of the same and shall use all reasonable endeavours to comply with the terms and conditions of any Agreement contained herein.
Notification of Changes The Company reserves the right to change these conditions from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of
the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. If there are any changes to our privacy policy, we will announce that
these changes have been made on our home page and on other key pages on our site. If there are any changes in how we use our site customers’
Personally Identifiable Information, notification by e-mail or postal mail will be made to those affected by this change. Any changes to our
privacy policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to these changes taking place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement
on a regular basis These terms and conditions form part of the Agreement between the Client and ourselves. Your accessing of this website and/or
undertaking of a booking or Agreement indicates your understanding, agreement to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms
and Conditions contained herein.
The Williams Brothers Corporation of America
Corporate Office
1330 Progress Drive
Front Royal, Virginia 22630
Distribution Centers:
WBCA Group Companies: Strike First Corporation Of America | AG Laser Technology
| Safety 1 Industries
